(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) So a big pet peeve of mine is
when we're working with a realtor on the
other side and they themselves multiple times say
I've never done a creative deal like this
before to get a house sold.
We're helping the buyers and yet they try
to lead the way with all these random
amendments and additional language that starts to convolute
the deal.
It drives me crazy but this is what
you see uh kind of on the back
end that we try to save our clients
from.
My question to those realtors is if you've
never danced salsa before and you're in a
salsa and with the salsa instructor my question
to these realtors is if you've never danced
salsa before and you're in a salsa class
why would you not follow the instructor's lead?
Why would you then try to lead the
instructor and tell them hey I've been doing
this game for this many years and so
I I should be the one leading this.
That's one of the pet peeves but long
story short the Acaba Home Team we do
creative deals all day long.
We do deals that other people could not
get done.
The home that we're going to close on
is a duplex that's been sitting for over
200 days because it needs a good amount
of work.
We figured out a win-win structure to
where all the work's getting done and covered
by the deal itself meaning our client's going
to get a brand new roof on the
house, brand new HVAC units in both units
and furnaces in both units.
They're going to get updated kitchens, updated bathrooms,
fresh paint on the inside.
They're going to get a portion of their
furnishing cost covered all within the deal because
of the way that we worked it.
So long story short a little bit of
venting on the creative piece but I do
enjoy putting these together and the Acaba Home
Team does it differently than most realtors out
there.